Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual materials, Series 14
  - World Wide Developers Conference videotapes, Subseries 14.7
    - Copland. Copland configuration management. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 16; Tape 106; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 58, Videotape 9)
    - Copland. Managing document content. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 108; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 58, Videotape 10)
    - Copland. Decline and fall of the event loop. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 109; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 1)
    - Copland. Copland text. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 110; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 2)
    - Copland. More Copland runtime. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 111; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 3)
    - Copland. Copland runtime. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 112; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (45 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 4)
    - Copland. Copland graphics & font rendering. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 114; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 5)
    - Copland. Copland I/O overview. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 115; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 6)
    - OpenDoc. Cyberdog unleashed. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 201; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 7)
    - OpenDoc. Cyberdog: building Internet components. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 202; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 8)
    - OpenDoc. Adding Internet to your application. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 203; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 9)
    - OpenDoc. Cross platform OpenDoc. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 204; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 59, Videotape 10)
    - OpenDoc. The business of software components. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 205; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 1)
    - OpenDoc. How to componentize your software. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 206; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 2)
    - OpenDoc. Open Doc & Copland. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 207; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 3)
    - OpenDoc. Getting started with OpenDoc & Cyberdog. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 208; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 4)
    - OpenDoc. Advanced OpenDoc tips & tricks. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 209; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 5)
    - OpenDoc. OpenDoc: shared work on the Internet. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 210; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 6)
    - Interactive media. Cross-platform QuickTime. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 17; Tape 309; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 7)
    - Interactive media. QuickTime conferencing on the Internet. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 311; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (80 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 8)
    - Internet & Apple communications. The Macintosh Internet technology platform. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 15; Tape 401; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 9)
    - Development tools. Java programming on the Macintosh. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 16; Tape 602; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 60, Videotape 10)
    - Development tools. Tools for dynamic web applications. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 16; Tape 604; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 1)
    - New media authoring. Authoring and design for the World Wide Web. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 13; Tape 1203; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 2)
    - New media authoring. Authoring for the next new media standard. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 14; Tape 1213; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 3)
    - Sponsored sessions. Natural intelligence. -- (Apple Worldwide Developers Conference, May 13-17, 1996), 1996 May 16; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (45 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 4)
  - Apple Library Cataloged videotapes, Subseries 14.8
    This subseries includes videotapes that had been catalogued by Apple Computer, Inc.'s corporate library. Includes videotapes dealing with a wide range of topics, including commercials, conferences, speeches, trade shows, etc.
    - Apple IIe introduction, revision 2. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1982; VT/1/1982; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 5)
      Apple Computer, Inc.
    - LISA, soul of a new computer [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1983; VT/5/1983; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 6)
    - Everything you always wanted to know about microcomputers but were afraid to ask: EYAWTKAMBWATA [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., undated; VT/6; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 7)
      Microcomputers; Apple II (Computer); Apple III (Computer); Apple Computer, Inc.; Riggenbach, Rod
    - John Sculley talks to Apple about Apple [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1983; VT/16/1983; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 61, Videotape 8)
      Executive speeches -- Sculley, John; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leading the way, chat with John Sculley [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1983; VT/27/1983; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 61, Videotape 9)
      Includes Christmas message
      Sculley, John; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leading the way, chat with John Sculley [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1983; VT/27/1983; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 61, Videotape 10)
    - Leadership forum, Warren Bennis [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/43/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 62, Videotape 1)
      Management; Leadership forum; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - The story of Macintosh [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/44/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (16 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 62, Videotape 2)
      Macintosh -- History; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leadership forum, R. Zaphiropoulos [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., undated; VT/47; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 62, Videotape 3)
      Management; Leadership forum; Apple Computer, Inc.; R. Zaphiropoulos
    - Lisa, it works the way you do [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/48/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 62, Videotape 4)
      Lisa; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Lisa, it works the way you do [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/48/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 62, Videotape 5)
    - Someday is here [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/51/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 62, Videotape 6)
      Apple IIc (Computer); Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Someday is here [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/51/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 62, Videotape 7)
    - 1984 [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/53/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (1 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 62, Videotape 8)
      Advertising commercials, Macintosh; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Apple savings and investment plan [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/60/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (11:06 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 62, Videotape 9)
      Apple Computer, Inc. -- Savings; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leadership forum, Lee Iacocca [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/60/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 62, Videotape 10)
    - Leadership forum, Lee Iacocca [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/60/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 63, Videotape 1)
    - Leadership forum, Lee Iacocca [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., c1984; VT/65/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 63, Videotape 2)
      Management; Leadership forum; Apple Computer, Inc.; Iacocca, Lee
    - John Sculley 4th quarter message: executive briefing tour [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 Aug. 24; VT/75/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (15 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 63, Videotape 3)
    - John Sculley 4th quarter message: executive briefing tour [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 Sept. 28; VT/75/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (39:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 63, Videotape 4)
    - John Sculley 4th quarter message: executive briefing tour [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 Sept. 28; VT/75/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (39:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 63, Videotape 5)
    - John Sculley 4th quarter message: executive briefing tour [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 Sept. 29; VT/75/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (40 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 63, Videotape 6)
    - Leadership forum, Fred Smith [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/76/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 63, Videotape 7)
      Leadership forum; Microdynamics; Management; Smith, Fred; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leadership forum, Fred Smith [Videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/76/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 63, Videotape 8)
      Leadership forum; Microdynamics; Management; Apple Computer, Inc.; Smith, Fred
    - Leadership forum, Bill Gates, part 1 [Videotape]: future of software. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/80A/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 63, Videotape 9)
      Leadership forum; Future -- Software applications; Management; Apple Computer, Inc.; Gates, Bill
    - Annual shareholders meeting, January 23, 1984. -- Cupertino, Calif. [note: actually 1985 shareholders meeting held at De Anza College], VT/92/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 63, Videotape 10)
      Apple Computer, Inc. -- Stockholders; Apple Computer, Inc. -- Shareholders; Apple Computer, Inc. -- Conferences; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Bluebusters [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/95/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 64, Videotape 1)
      Macintosh (Computer); IBM
    - Leadership forum, William Fruend [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1985; VT/101; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 64, Videotape 2)
      Management; Leadership forum; William Fruend; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Statement of direction [videotape] / John Sculley. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1985; VT/101; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 64, Videotape 3)
      Management; Leadership forum; Apple Computer, Inc.; Freund, William
    - Leadership forum, Steven Wheelwright [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; VT/120/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (50:05 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 64, Videotape 4)
      Executive speeches -- Wheelwright, Steven; Management; Leadership forum; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leadership forum, David Norman [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; VT/123/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (58:56 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 64, Videotape 5)
      Leadership forum; Executive speeches -- Norman, David; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Leadership forum, Cathleen Black [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; VT/127/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (101:24 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 64, Videotape 6)
      Leadership forum; Management; Executive speeches -- Black, Cathleen; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Seeds of change [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; VT/153/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (14:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 64, Videotape 7)
      Apple Computer, Inc.; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Seeds of change [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1986; VT/153/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (14:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 64, Videotape 8)
    - AppleWorld engineering 1987 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/165/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 64, Videotape 9)
      Macintosh SE (Computer); Macintosh II (Computer); Apple Computer, Inc.
    - AppleWorld engineering 1987 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/165/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 64, Videotape 10)
    - Getting close to the customer [videotape] / Billy Landin. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984 Apr. 10; VT/165/1986; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 65, Videotape 1)
      Macintosh II (Computer); Macintosh SE (Computer); Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Apple II forever (1984: April 24: San Francisco, CA.) [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1989; VT/179/1989; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (113:47 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 65, Videotape 2)
      Apple Computer, Inc. -- Conferences; Products, new -- Introduction -- Apple II; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Ripples [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/185/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 65, Videotape 3)
      Apple 10 year anniversary video; pebble dropped into pond; ripples extend from splash; visual montage of Apple history - Jobs, Wozniak, old Apple computers, CG images, TV commercial excerpts, print ads, Annual Sales Conference and Shareholders' Meeting excerpts, screen shots, Apple executives. Closes with logo, "power", (c) 1987.
      Apple Computer, Inc. -- Ten year retrospective; Apple World -- Presentation; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Keeper of the culture [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1984; VT/192/1984; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 65, Videotape 4)
      Corporate culture.; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Knowledge navigator [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/224/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 65, Videotape 5)
      Future technologies; Computers -- Future applications; Computers and education; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Knowledge navigator [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/224/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 65, Videotape 6)
      Computers -- Future applications; Computers and education; Future technologies; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Employee communications meeting, Q1 FY 88 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/225/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 65, Videotape 7)
      Employee communications meeting; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - EDUCOM '87 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/234/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (38:58 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 65, Videotape 8)
      EDUCOM -- Conferences; Apple Computer, Inc. -- Conferences; Executive speeches -- Sculley, John; EDUCOM; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - John Sculley keynote address at MacWorld '88 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/237; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (33 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 65, Videotape 9)
      Executive speeches -- Sculley, John; MacWorld 1988; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - John Sculley keynote address at MacWorld '88 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1987; VT/237; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (33 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 65, Videotape 10)
    - Beginner's luck [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/246/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 1)
      Computers -- Buyer's guide; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Project 2000 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/247/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (11:50 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 66, Videotape 2)
      Future applications; Son of Knowledge navigator; Navigator II; Computers.; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Project 2000 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/247/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (11:50 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 66, Videotape 3)
    - Model for a new era [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/252/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 4)
      Information management; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Human interface [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/254/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 5)
      Human interface; Computer user interface; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Employee communication meeting, Q3, FY 88 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/279/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (140:08 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 6)
      Employee communications meeting; Computer networks.; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Worldwide meeting, February 9-10, 1987 [videotape]: strategies and criteria. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/280/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 7)
      Corporate strategies; Apple Computer, Inc.; Wheelwright, Steven
    - Worldwide meeting, February 9-10, 1987 [videotape]: Apple's identity, goals, and strategy. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/286/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 8)
      Executive speeches -- Sculley, John; Corporate strategy; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Open Door [videotape]: short version. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/287/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (9:31 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 66, Videotape 9)
      Music; Macintosh (Computer); MIDI; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Open door [videotape]: long version. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/288/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (33 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 66, Videotape 10)
      MIDI; Music; Macintosh (Computer); Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Open door [videotape]: long version. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/288/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (33 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 67, Videotape 1)
    - Open door [videotape]: long version. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/288/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (35 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 67, Videotape 2)
      MIDI; Macintosh (Computer); Music; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - In search of excellence [Videotape], c1985; VT/289/1985; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (90 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 67, Videotape 3)
      Examines successful American businesses by focusing on themes of innovation, productivity through people and shared values. IBM, Apple Computers, McDonald's and Disney World serve as examples in a behind the scenes look at their operations.
      Industrial management -- U.S.; Economics; Sociology; Management; McDonald's Corporation; Apple Computer, Inc.; Walt Disney World (Fla.); Peters, Tomas J.
    - Open Apple Q3, FY 1988 update with Del Yocam [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/306/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 67, Videotape 4)
      Finance -- Forecasting; Open Apple; Childcare Center; Yocam, Del; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Open Apple Q3, FY 1988 update with Del Yocam [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/306/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 67, Videotape 5)
      Finance -- Forecasting; Open Apple; Yocam, Del; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Pencil test [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/307/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 67, Videotape 6)
      Siggraph; Macintosh -- Computer animation; Apple Computer, Inc. Advanced Development Group (Eraserhead Team)
    - Employee communication meeting, Q4, FY 88 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/311/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 67, Videotape 7)
    - Employee communication meeting, Q4, FY 88 [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/311/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 67, Videotape 8)
    - Claris story [videotape]: story and product demonstrations [videotape]. -- Palo Alto, Calif.: Claris Corp., 1988; VT/314/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (29:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 67, Videotape 9)
      Software -- Demonstrations; Claris Corporation -- History; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - New chapter [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/315/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (8:49 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 67, Videotape 10)
      Adult literacy; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - HyperGold [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/316/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 68, Videotape 1)
      Human resource personnel manager -- Tutorials; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Open Apple Q4, FY 1987 [videotape]. -- (Employee video magazine series). -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., VT/318/1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (14:55 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 68, Videotape 2)
      Finance -- Forecasting; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - New enterprise [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/327; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (14:55 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 68, Videotape 3)
      Administration -- Techniques; Apple Computer, Inc.
    - Information protection [videotape]. -- Cupertino, Calif.: Apple Computer, Inc., 1988; VT/333/1988; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (6:31 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 68, Videotape 4)